Hand it over!
أعطوني إياها
Is this what you wanted, Chiffon?
أهذا ما أردته يا شيفون؟
Yes! Thank you, Bege!
أجل، شكرًا لك يا بيجي
But we definitely took on a big headache!
لكننا جلبنا المتاعب معنا
Honestly, getting away is now more important than the assassination!
بصراحة، الهرب أهم من إتمام عملية الاغتيال الآن
What are you saying, Bege?!
ما الذي تتفوه به يا بيجي؟
We decided to help Nami and the others get away safely!
قررنا مساعدة نامي والآخرين على الهروب بسلام
We can't just give up halfway simply because we want to save ourselves!
لا يمكننا التخلّي عن قرارنا فجأة لرغبتنا بالنجاة
This is how one repays their debt!
بهذه الطريقة ستسد دينك لهم
Mm-hm!
أجل
Rero !
ريرو
It's going to be all right! Believe in the taste of the cake!
لا داعي للقلق، ثقوا بالكعكة
Black Leg is truly an amazing cook!
فالساق السوداء طاهٍ مذهل بحق
Man! This is why I love you, Chiffon!
بحق، لهذا السبب أحبك يا شيفون
Madam!
سيدتنا
Wedding cake!
كعكة الزفاف
Let's shake them off, guys!
لنضللهم يا رجال
Yeah!
أجل
It's Commander Smoothie's ship!
إنّها سفينة سموذي-ساما
Commander Smoothie!
سموذي-ساما
Mistress Citron! Mistress Cinnamon!
سترون-ساما، سينامون-ساما
Are you ready, Straw Hats?
هل أنتم مستعدون لملاقاة مصيركم يا طاقم قبعة القش؟
Another fleet is on our tail!
سفينة أخرى تطاردنا
It's Sweet Commander Smoothie's ship!
إنّها سفينة قائدة الحلوى سموذي
Big Mom is gone, but now there's a sweet commander!
بعد أن ارتحنا من بيغ مام نجد أنفسنا مطاردين من أحد قادة الحلوى
It's that woman who squeezes stuff...
إنّها تلك المرأة التي تعصر الأشياء
Sister Smoothie!
...أختي سموذي
How much longer until we reach Cacao Island?
كم سنستغرق للوصول إلى جزيرة الكاكاو؟
A little over three hours from now!
أكثر من ثلاث ساعات بقليل
We'll get there at around one a.m., just as we promised!
سنصل في تمام الساعة الواحدة صباحًا كما اتفقنا
But we don't know where or when Luffy is going to appear on Cacao Island,
ولكننا لا نعلم أين ومتى سيظهر لوفي في جزيرة الكاكاو
and we have no way to tell him it's dangerous!
ولا يمكننا تحذيره حتّى
There's only one plan I can think of for us to get past Cacao Island.
خطرت في بالي خطة لدخول جزيرة الكاكاو
Minister Oven! Our fleets are slowly surrounding the island!
أوفن-ساما، العديد من السفن وصلت للإحاطة بالجزيرة
Is this really necessary?!
أنحن حقًّا بحاجة لهذا العدد الكبير؟
There's no way Commander Katakuri will let Straw Hat escape, anyway!
لا أظن أنّ كاتاكوري-ساما سيدع قبعة القش لوفي يُفلت منه
Tell that to Tamago and Mont d'Or!
لا أعلم، اسأل تاماغو ومونت دور
It's necessary, Big Brother Oven!
نحتاجهم جميعًا يا أخي أوفن
Can you believe it?!
...أتصدق
That big explosion of the chateau was planned, too!
أنّ الانفجار الضخم للقصر كان متعمّدًا وضمن خطتهم أيضًا؟
What?!
ماذا؟
Even though they're a small group of rookies, we cannot underestimate them!
حتّى لو كانوا مبتدئين وعددهم قليل، فلا تقللوا من شأنهم
If they escape, we'll be humiliated beyond repair!
إن هربوا منّا، فستكون وصمة عار على جبيننا
Don't worry... They won't get past us here!
لا تقلق، سننال منهم هنا بكل تأكيد
Listen! About three hours from now, at one a.m.,
اسمعوا، بعد ثلاث ساعات تقريبًا، في الساعة الواحدة صباحًا
the separated members of the Straw Hat crew will meet up here at Cacao Island.
سيجتمع أفراد طاقم قبعة القش المنفصلين هنا على جزيرة الكاكاو
Think of it as your last chance to kill them all!
اعتبروها فرصتكم الأخيرة للقضاء عليهم
Yes, sir!
حاضر
If by any chance Straw Hat appears, he'll come out of a mirror on the island!
إن كان قبعة القش سيظهر على هذه الجزيرة فسيكون ذلك عبر أحد المرايا بلا شك
Everyone, go and break every mirror in this town.
لذا اذهبوا جميعًا إلى منازلكم وحطّموا جميع المرايا في البلدة
Didn't you hear me?! Just do it!
ألم تسمعوني؟ هيّا تحرّكوا
No way! Even the precious mirrors?!
محال، حتّى المرايا الثمينة؟
He's an ability user. If you have a mirror that you don't want to break, throw it into the sea.
بما أنّه مستخدم لفاكهة شيطان فالمرايا التي لا تريدون كسرها يجب أن ترموها في البحر
You can retrieve it later! Anyway...
ويمكنكم إخراجها من البحر لاحقًا
this is the only mirror that will remain on the island!
يجب أن تكون هذه المرآة الوحيدة السليمة على هذه الجزيرة
There must be no others!
لا أريد وجود أي واحدة غيرها
If anyone allows Straw Hat to escape from one of their mirrors,
إن سمح أي شخص بخروج قبعة القش من مرآته
we will execute their entire family!
فسيُعدم هو وعائلته بأكملها
Hurry up!
أسرعوا
Y-Yes, sir!
مـ-مفهوم
Don't think you can get away, Straw Hat!
لا تظن أنّك ستهرب يا قبعة القش
For you, this isn't an exit...
بالنسبة لك، هذا لن يكون مخرجًا
it's the entrance to hell!
بل مدخل إلى الجحيم
My apologies...
...اعذرني
It was foolish of me to not notice her needles.
فلم ألحظ أيًّا من إبرها الصغيرة، كانت حماقةً منّي
In a duel between pirates, there's no such thing as playing dirty.
في معارك القراصنة، لا يوجد شيء اسمه قتال قذر
Not being able to dodge them was my fault!
الخطأ يقع على عاتقي لكوني لم أستطع تفاديها
I no longer think...
...أنا لم أعد
that you're below my level!
أعتبرك خصمًا أقل شأنًا منّي
Is that so?! I'm glad to hear it!
حقًّا؟ يسعدني ذلك
Thanks!
شكرًا لك
But...
...لكنني
I'm gonna win!
سأنتصر
Ouch!
مؤلم
You have no time to rest!
لا وقت للراحة، ولا طعام حتّى تتمكن من تفادي الهجمات 100 مرة
What?!
ماذا؟
If you think that sounds bad, then concentrate!
ما دام الأمر يبدو لك فظيعًا، فركز
I found you!
هنا
Ouch!
مؤلم
Your enemy won't always be in front of you...
لن يهجم خصمك دومًا من الأمام
It's easy to read animals' minds because they show all of their emotions.
يسهل توقع تحركات الحيوانات لأنّها تُظهر كل مشاعرها
But... humans are different... We can defy expectations and cheat others.
لكن البشر على النقيض تمامًا لأنّه يمكننا مخالفة التوقعات وخداع الآخرين
"Growwwl"
دمدمة
Ouch!
مؤلم
I'm hungry, Rayleigh!
أنا جائع يا ريلي
Do you think your enemy will care if you're hungry?
هل سيتوقف عدوك عن مهاجمتك لأنّك جائع؟
Every attack has an intent...
لكل هجوم إرادة
Ow!
مؤلم
and a presence!
وهيئة
I smell something delicious.
أشتم رائحة شيء لذيذ
That's my dinner. Don't pay it any mind.
هذه رائحة عشائي، لا تفكّر به
There you are!
هنا
There!
هناك
Don't just attack blindly, Luffy!
لا تهاجم بشكل عشوائي يا لوفي
Rayleigh, that hurts! I can feel your anger!
هذا مؤلم يا ريلي، أشعر بغضبك
That is also haki!
هذا هاكي أيضًا
Sharpen your senses!
اصقل حواسك
Ouch!
مؤلم
Feel your enemy's presence!
استشعر وجود عدوك
I can feel your anger!
أستشعر غضبك
Damn...
سحقًا
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Go away, you guys...
غادرا
I don't want any food.
لا أريد طعامًا
Rayleigh said I can't eat, so I won't eat!
ريلي حرّم عليّ الطعام، لذا لن أتناول شيئًا
Focus, Luffy.
ركز يا لوفي
Luffy...
...لوفي
It's all part of observation haki, but... You're more proficient in sensing the feelings of living things.
يبدو أنّ هاكي الملاحظة لديك قادر على الإحساس بمشاعر المرء والحيوانات
Huh? Is that so?
ماذا؟ حقًّا؟
But if you have that ability,
لكن امتلاكك لهذه القدرة
I'm sure you'll be able to sense your opponent's moves, too.
يعني أنّه سيكون بوسعك الإحساس بتحركات خصمك بلا شك
Uh-huh.
أجل
There are some strong people in this world capable of seeing a bit into the future.
يوجد بعض الأقوياء في العالم قادرون على رؤية لمحة من المستقبل
The future?!
المستقبل؟
What will you do when you face them?
ماذا ستفعل إن واجهت أحدهم؟
With only two years of training, you won't gain that ability.
سنتين من التدريب ليست كافية لإيصالك إلى مستواهم
You'll have a rough time.
سيكون أمرًا شاقًّا عليك
It depends on what kind of person they are.
الأمر يعتمد على شخصية خصمي
What? Your opponent's character?! Does that matter to you?
ماذا؟ شخصية خصمك؟ هل هذا يهمك؟
I've never thought of it like that.
لم يسبق لي أن فكرت من هذا المنظور
Of course!
بالطبع يهمني
You're quite the character.
يا لك من فتى غريب الأطوار
It matters! Like when I can't escape...
هذا يهم، فمثلًا عندما لا يكون هنالك مهرب
I think you'll have trouble in the future.
أظن أنّك ستواجه أوقاتًا عصيبة
There's no time for you to rest.
لا وقت لدينا للراحة
What?
ماذا؟
Let's continue the training. Come with me!
سننتقل إلى التدريب التالي، اتبعني
Okay!
أجل
I'll teach you everything I can.
سأعلّمك كل ما بجعبتي
Grilled Mochi!
الموتشي الحارقة
If we get caught, we'll be killed-rero !
سنُقتل إن قبضوا علينا-ريرو
We have the cake.
بحوزتنا الكعكة
They can't just attack us!
لذا لا يمكنهم مهاجمتنا
When Prometheus gets that big,
كما أنّ ضخامة بروميثيوس تمنعه من التحرك بسرعة
We'll reach Liqueur Island soon!
سنصل إلى جزيرة الخمر قريبًا
It wasn't hard at all. All because we fixed the paddles in time.
لم يكن الأمر صعبًا، وذلك لأننا أصلحنا المجاديف في الوقت المناسب
Good job, guys!
أحسنتم يا رجال
Thanks! That's kind of you!
أجل، هذا لطف منك
We'll dump the cake at Liqueur Island and make our great escape-rero !
سنضع الكعكة في جزيرة الخمر ثم نلوذ بالفرار-ريرو
Yeah, that sounds good.
أجل، تبدو خطة جيدة
Not yet.
كلا، ليس بعد
What's wrong, Chiffon?!
ما الخطب يا شيفون؟
Liqueur Island is too close!
جزيرة الخمر قريبة للغاية لذا لنستدرجهم إلى جزيرة المعجنات
Hey! Are you out of your mind?!
مهلًا، هل جُننتِ؟
If Mama eats the cake at Liqueur Island and comes to, out of her ravenous rampage,
إن تناولت ماما التي تعاني حاليًّا من نوبة الجوع الكعكة على جزيرة الخمر واستعادت وعيها
there will still be enough time for her to catch up to the ship belonging to Nami's group!
فسيكون لديها وقتًا كافيًا لمطاردة سفينة نامي والآخرين
So what?! We've done enough already!
وماذا في ذلك؟ ساعدناهم كفاية
We're gonna die! Look!
...سنموت إن فعلنا ذلك، انظري
Mama is even hungrier now!
إلى مدى جوع ماما الآن
I wanna eat it!
...أريد تناولها
I wanna eat it already!
...أريد تناولها حالًا
Wedding cake...
...كعكة الزفاف
I wanna eat it! I really wanna eat it!
أريد تناولها... أريد تناولها
Do you understand, Chiffon?
هل فهمتِ يا شيفون؟
Yes.
أجل
Let's go to Puffs Island.
لنذهب إلى جزيرة المعجنات
You weren't listening!
لم تصنتِ إليّ
I'll pay my debt to Straw Hat and the others, even if it costs me my life!
سأردّ المعروف إلى طاقم قبعة القش حتّى لو كلّفني ذلك حياتي
That's what I have decided!
هذا ما قررته سلفًا
So I'll go by myself if I have to!
لذا سأذهب وحدي
Change course! We'll head to Puffs Island!
تغيّر في الخطة، سنتجه إلى جزيرة المعجنات
What?!
ماذا؟
That's my wife!
هذه ماهية زوجتي
I love you even more, Chiffon!
أحبك حبًّا جمًّا يا شيفون
Let's go, guys!
هيّا بنا يا رجال
Okay, Father!
عُلم يا فاذر
I'll see you later.
أراكم حينها
Be careful, Sanji.
توخّى الحذر يا سانجي
Of course!
أجل
D-Don't come close! Stay away! Sanji...
لـ-لا تقترب، ابتعد يا سانجي
...-san !
سان-
I'll leave the Sunny in your hands! We're entering the final stage!
اعتمد عليكم في حماية السفينة، فسندخل مرحلة حاسمة
Yeah!
أجل
Pudding-chan, take me to Cacao Island.
بودينغ-تشان، لنذهب إلى جزيرة الكاكاو
Don't tell me what to do! And don't act like a bossy husband!
لا تملي عليّ الأوامر فلا يحق لك التصرف معي كزوج متسلّط يا سانجي
...-san !
سان-
Oh? What was that?
ماذا؟ ما كان ذلك؟
Carrot!
كاروت
Are you okay now?!
هل أنتِ بخير الآن؟
I'm sorry, everyone... I was sleeping.
أنا أعتذر يا رفاق، كنتُ نائمة
No need to apologize! You did great, Little Sis!
لا داعي للاعتذار فلقد بذلتِ مجهودًا مذهلًا يا أختي الصغيرة
Can Nekomamushi and Inuarashi do that when they see the full moon too, Little Sis?
أيمكن لنيكوماموشي وإينواراشي أن يفعلا ذات الشيء حين ينظران إلى القمر المكتمل؟
Uh-huh!
أجل
Both Master Nekomamushi and Duke Inuarashi are capable of becoming much stronger than I was!
الزعيم نيكوماموشي والدوق وإينواراشي يصبحان أقوى منّي بكثير حين يتحولان
Really?!
حقًّا؟
Keep watch and tell me which direction their attacks come from!
راقبوا وأخبروني من أي اتجاه تأتي هجماتهم
Got it!
مفهوم
No!
كلا
I need even more liquid.
ما زلتُ بحاجة إلى المزيد من السوائل
You're hurting your own men! You're going too far!
إنّكِ تؤذين أتباعك، لقد تماديتِ كثيرًا
There's no way I'm letting the Straw Hat crew get away!
لن أدع طاقم قبعة القش يلوذ بالفرار
What's that?!
ما ذلك؟
Is she a giant?
أهي من العمالقة؟
Can I see your panties...
...أيمكنني رؤية ملابسكِ الداخـ
Stop it, you pervy skeleton!
كفّ عن ذلك أيها الهيكل العظمي المنحرف
It's coming again!
إنّها قادمة مجدّدًا
Dodge to the right!
نحو اليمين
Again, to the right!
نحو اليمين مجدّدًا
Jinbe, to the left!
جينبي، نحو اليسار
That damn Jinbe!
جينبي اللعين
Stay alert! I'm depending on your directions!
واصلوا على هذا المنوال، فأنا اعتمد على توجهياتكم
You can count on us!
اعتمد علينا
Don't worry! I'll take responsibility!
لا تقلق، سأتولى الأمر
Oh, she became even bigger!
ما زالت تزداد ضخامة
Smoothie! This ship can't handle your weight!
سموذي، لن تصمد السفينة
This will sink them!
هذا سيكون كفيلًا بإغراقهم
Here it comes!
إنّها قادمة
It's huge!
يا لضخامتها
It'll sink us!
ستُغرقنا
Dodge to the right, Jinbe!
نحو اليمين يا جينبي
Everyone, hang on tight!
تمسكوا جيّدًا جميعًا
Thank you, Pudding-chan.
شكرًا لكِ يا بودينغ-تشان على مساعدتي طوال هذا الوقت
Cut it out!
اخرس
Move over! Move over to the edge, Sanji...
ابتعد، ابتعد إلى حافة البساط يا سانجي
...-san !
سان-
People will think we're husband and wife!
سيظنوننا زوجين
Who will?
من سيظن ذلك؟
A-Anyway,
عـ-على أي حال
is this really gonna work out?!
هل ستنجح فيما ستفعله حقًّا؟
Luffy's gonna come out surrounded by fleets and armies.
سيظهر لوفي وسط حشدٍ من الأساطيل والجيوش
I will save my captain... no matter what!
وسأنقذ قبطاني مهما كلّف الثمن
What's going on with the mirrors?
ما أخبار المرايا؟
Minister Oven, we made sure that they were all disposed of, as you ordered.
كما نصّت أوامرك يا أوفن-ساما جعلناهم يتخلّصون من جميع المرايا
Your brothers and sisters are arriving one after another.
إخوتك وأخواتك يصلون واحدًا تلو الآخر
Okay.
هكذا إذًا
I can't believe this many members of the family have assembled here on Cacao Island.
لا أصدّق أنّ هذا العدد الهائل من أفراد العائلة قد اجتمعوا هنا على جزيرة الكاكاو
Just how wary of Straw Hat Luffy are they?!
ما مدى قلقهم من قبعة القش لوفي؟
How many enemies are there? Tens of thousands?
هل يبلغ عدد الأعداء عشرات الآلاف؟
I think they have less than ten.
أظنهم أقل من 10 أشخاص
What?! I'm gonna take a nap.
ماذا؟ سآخذ قيلولة
Wake me up when something happens!
أيقظني إن حدث شيء ما
Yes, sir!
حاضر
The Worst Generation, huh?
الجيل الأسوأ؟
I can't let them have their way anymore,
سأضع لهم حدًّا على هذه الجزيرة
what with my pride of being a former sweet commander...
بكبريائي كقائد حلوى سابق
Summoning all of our forces to fight such a small group,
استدعاء كل هذه القوّات لمحاربة تلك المجموعة الصغيرة
brings shame to the name of Emperor Big Mom.
لهو عارٌ على سمعة الإمبراطورة بيغ مام
Or is Straw Hat Luffy that formidable?
أو أنّ قبعة القش لوفي آهلٌ لهذه الدرجة؟
Are you serious, Big Brother Oven?!
هل أنت جاد يا أخي أوفن؟
It's like a festival!
وكأننا في مهرجان
Looks like fun!
يبدو الأمر ممتعًا
Shut up! I know you guys have nothing better to do! Just follow the plan.
اخرسوا، أعلم أنّه لا يوجد لديكم ما تفعلونه، لذا تماشوا مع الأمر
That damn Straw Hat... He humiliated us at the tea party.
قبعة القش اللعين، لقد أهاننا في حفلة الشاي
I'll get revenge by killing him!
سأنتقم عبر قتله
When we were deployed as the enraged army,
عندما أُرسل جيشنا الغاضب للقبض عليه
we should have killed him...
كان يجدر بنا قتله
Then, we wouldn't have failed at the tea party.
ما كنا حينها سنتعرض للمتاعب في حفلة الشاي
Usually, we can easily discern an invader's movements...
لطالما كان بإمكاننا رصد تحركات الدخلاء بسهولة
It's so inconvenient without the territorial sea slugs!
أما الآن، فالأمر صعب من دون رخويات الإقليم البحري
But our preparations are thorough, and we still have an hour and a half.
لكننا على أهبة الاستعداد وما زال أمامنا ساعة ونصف
When the time comes, they're finished!
عندما يحين الوقت، فستكون نهايتهم
The Straw Hat crew's planned rendezvous at Cacao Island
الموعد المحدد للقاء طاقم قبعة القش على جزيرة الكاكاو
is approximately one hour away.
تبقى عليه ساعة تقريبًا
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
ما الخطب يا قبعة القش؟
Is this...
...أهذا
Yeah, that's right.
أجل، هذا صحيح
...the end?!
كل ما لديك؟
Okay. I'll take you on.
أجل، سأقبل ذلك
I'm going to end this!
سأنهي الأمر
If you can withstand this...
...إن تمكنتَ من الصمود أمام هذا
I have already given you my answer...
لقد أجبتك سلفًا
This is the end...
فستحين النهاية
Yeah.
أجل
Gear Fourth!
المحرك الرابع
Snakeman!
الرجل الأفعى
Snakeman? It's a little different than before.
الرجل الأفعى؟ تبدو هيئتك مختلفة عمّا سبق
Your observation haki sure is something...
هاكي الملاحظة لديك مذهل بلا شك
That's why I'm using...
...لهذا السبب سأستخدم
something faster!
شيئًا أسرع
Why use such a simple attack at this stage in the fight?
لِمَ فعّل هذا الطور بعد كل ذلك الوقت؟
What is going on?
ما الذي يحدث؟
Why is it coming from the side?
لِمَ أتت من هذا الجانب؟
Where did it come from?!
من أين هاجمني؟
I'm sure I dodged it!
متأكد أنني تفاديتها
I see... That's how it works!
فهمت، هكذا هو الأمر
Chase him, Python!
طارده يا بايثون
It's no use!
لا جدوى
It accelerates even though it's stretching!
ستتسارع حتّى أثناء التمدد
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Jet...
مدفع
Culverin!
الأفعى النفاث
This is far from over!
لم ينتهِ الأمر بعد
I'm stronger and faster than you!
إنني أقوى وأسرع منك
Catch up to him!
الحق به
Diced Mochi!
الموتشي المقطعة
The mochi is so sticky...
...الموتشي لزجة جدًّا
and I can't get it off!
ولا أستطيع الإفلات منها
I feel dizzy!
أشعر بالدوار
Stop! What are you doing?!
توقف، ما الذي تفعله؟
Put me down!
أنزلني
Damn! I can't pull myself apart!
سحقًا، لا أستطيع تخليص نفسي منها
This is the end, Straw Hat!
حانت نهايتك يا قبعة القش
Dammit!
اللعنة
Damn!
سحقًا
It hurts!
هذا مؤلم
This sucks!
هذا صعب
I'm so hungry!
أنا جائع
What the hell are you saying?!
ما الذي تتفوه به؟
I'm saying what's on my mind!
قلتُ كل ما يدور في ذهني
I feel better now!
أشعر بتحسن الآن
Fall already, Katakuri!
فلتسقط يا كاتاكوري
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Jet Culverin!
مدفع الأفعى النفاث
Punch Mochi!
قبضات الموتشي
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
مؤلم، مؤلم، مؤلم
Go, Python!
انطلق يا بايثون
Grilled Mochi!
الموتشي الحارقة
Damn!
سحقًا
What's next?
ما الهجمة التالية؟
How interesting!
مثيرٌ للاهتمام
Bring it on!
آتني بها
Here I come!
ها أنا ذا
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Black Mamba!
أفعى مامبا السوداء
One more attack and it'll be over, Straw Hat!
هجمة أخرى وبعدها ستحين نهايتك يا قبعة القش
I'll take you down no matter what it takes, Katakuri!
حتمًا سأطيح بك يا كاتاكوري
That one again!
تلك الهجمة مجدّدًا
I'll put you out of your misery!
سأخلّصك من ألمك
I don't need you to!
لا داعي لذلك
Now I remember.
بالمناسبة
I wonder if Monkey-chan's doing all right.
أتظن أنّ مونكي-تشان بخير؟
Rise above it, Luffy...
كن بالقمة يا لوفي
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Diced Mochi!
الموتشي المقطعة
King Cobra!
ملك الكوبرا
You can't get away now!
لن تهرب منّي بعد الآن
Go!
انطلق
Cacao Island
جزيرة الكاكاو
10:10 p.m.
الساعة 10:10 مساءً
Bege's Group At Sea
مجموعة بيجي في البحر
The Sunny
سفينة الساني
11:08 p.m.
الساعة 11:08 مساءً
11:36 p.m.
الساعة 11:36 مساءً
Brownie 32nd Son of the Charlotte Family
الابن 32 لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت براوني
Snack 25th Son of the Charlotte Family (Former Member of the Four Sweet Commanders) Bounty: 600 Million Belly
(الابن 25 لعائلة شارلوت (القائد الرابع سابق شارلوت سناك المكافأة: 600 مليون بيري
Snack 25th Son of the Charlotte Family (Former Member of the Four Sweet Commanders) Bounty: 600 Million Belly
(الابن 25 لعائلة شارلوت (القائد الرابع سابق شارلوت سناك المكافأة: 600 مليون بيري
Joconde 27th Daughter of the Charlotte Family
الابنة 27 لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت جوكوند
Decuplets 36-40th Sons and 30-34th Daughters of the Charlotte Family
الأبناء من 36 إلى 40 والبنات من 30 إلى 34 عشرة توائم
Chiboust 30th Son of the Charlotte Family
الابن 30 لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت شيبوست
Raisin 33rd Son of the Charlotte Family
الابن 33 لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت ريزن
Yuen 35th Son of the Charlotte Family
الابن 35 لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت يوين
Myukuru 25th Daughter of the Charlotte Family
الابنة 25 لعائلة شارلوت شارلوت ميوكورو
12:05 a.m.
الساعة 12:05 صباحًا
LIQUEUR ISLAND
جزيرة الخمر
NUTS ISLAND
جزيرة المكسرات
PUFFS ISLAND
جزيرة المعجنات
CACAO ISLAND
جزيرة الكاكاو